Bradley Levick

(T) 07456 299 092

(A) 112 Parklands Rd, Hassocks, BN6 8LF.

(E) bradlevickdev@gmail.com

(W) www.brad-levick.squarespace.com

CAREER OBJECTIVES

From a young age I have enjoyed creating custom game content, from designing levels to creating my own games from scratch. It is my ambition to transition my passion, subsequent education and work experience in testing into a full time career working in the games industry. Over recent years I have worked with various BAFTA award winning companies as I strive towards acquiring a full time position in QA.

Developing games has long been my goal and motivation. I relish the opportunity to learn new skills and techniques and I am confident I could become a valuable asset to your team.

SKILLS

- Games testing and QA Localisation experience with an eye for detail
- Excellent problem solving and critical thinking skills
- Thorough bug detection and detailed reporting skills
- Experience with tracking & versioning tools and designing/interpreting test plans
- Experience with games engines and a detailed understanding of the development process
- Working to deadlines and performing under pressure
- Confident communicator, good written and verbal communication skills
- Literate in MS Office and a fast learner when it comes to new applications
- Good leadership skills, self driven with the ability to work autonomously or in a team

EXPERIENCE

October 2015

BITHELL GAMES, LONDON

VOLUME: CODA (PS4) - PLAYTESTER

- Worked with the level designer in London in testing each level during the development process
- Reported bugs that were detected, recorded steps to replicate issues and offered solutions
- Recorded information such as completion times and obstacles met during play
- Contributed to research and development for revised iterations
- Provided feedback directly regarding game-play experience and level cohesion

February 2015

ROLL7, LONDON

NOT A HERO (STEAM) – PLAYTESTER

- Prepared detailed reports and implemented tests as per test plan
- Reported bugs that were encountered and how to replicate them on closed developer forums
- · Completed research and development surveys and feedback sheets with recorded information
- Recorded and submitted game-play captures and hardware diagnostics when bugs were encountered

November 2014 – December 2014

PLUG-IN MEDIA, BRIGHTON

DORA AND FRIENDS - QA LOCALISATION – WORK EXPERIENCE

- Experience with project management / tracking tools (Trello)
- Worked with SVN version control
- Worked with Lead QA Tester utilizing debugging processes
- Responsible for localisation testing across various mobile devices
- Experience working in a professional AGILE environment
- Attended production meetings every morning to discuss progress and deadlines
- Designed and interpreted test plans
- Prepared detailed reports and implemented tests as per test plan
- Professional training with Unity

August 2014 - September 2014

TEAM17 DIGITAL, WEST YORKSHIRE

PENARIUM (STEAM) – PLAYTESTER

- Frequent contact with developers on closed forums and through direct messaging
- Prepared detailed reports and implemented tests as per test plan
- · Reported bugs that were encountered and how to replicate them on closed developer forums
- Recorded and submitted game-play captures as required when bugs were encountered

June 2014

FUTURLAB, BRIGHTON

VELOCITY 2X (PS4) – PLAYTESTER

- Worked with the company director, programmers and artists to test the game during the development process
- Reported bugs that were detected, recorded steps to replicate issues and offered solutions
- Recorded information such as completion times and obstacles met during play
- Prepared detailed reports and completed survey's and feedback sheets at the end of each level
- · Attended meetings with the development team to discuss game-play and offer critical feedback

Additionally, I also have considerable experience in managerial roles at flagship retail games stores, from which I have learned a great deal in leadership, organisation, performing under pressure and motivating staff. In these positions I have led both small and large teams to success in meeting company deadlines and surpassing targets.

EDUCATION

2009 - 2011

COLEG MENAI, LLANGEFNI

NATIONAL DIPLOMA INTERACTIVE MEDIA WITH GAME DESIGN

Awarded Triple Distinction - Achieved distinction grade in all 48 assignment modules

1998 - 2003

OATHALL COMMUNITY COLLEGE, WEST SUSSEX

GCSE: Science Double Award (C,C), Mathematics (B), English Literature (C), English Language (C), French (C), Design Technology Electronics (C), Art & Design (B), Physical Education (C)

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Game development, photo editing, drawing, sound design, gaming, airbrushing, basketball, TV & film, music and most importantly, my family.

For the past few years I have been a full time parent and where possible I am working on a small indie projects. I also enjoy learning about mobile developments and I intend on developing a game for tablets and smart-phones.

REFEREES

Sam Robinson

Freelance Level Designer, Volume: Coda Sam@onebitbeyond.com

Alan Owen

Technical Director, Plug-In Media Alan.owen@pluginmedia.net

Steve Gorst

Head of Games Development team, Coleg Menai Gorst1s@gllm.ac.uk

Additional references can be provided upon request